Subtitle Provide by dramacool.in Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.in [Admin.@YNG]
Sir, I truly apologize.
سيدي، أنا أعتذر حقا.
My mistake, my mistake.
خطئي، خطئي.
Enough of that, just make your choice.
كفى من ذلك، فقط اتخذ قرارك.
So this time, could you possibly...
إذن هذه المرة، هل من الممكن أن...
Lin Xiaoran.
لين شياوران.
You're actually here?
هل أنت هنا فعلا؟
Official Li, I...
الرسمي لي ، أنا...
We were just out for a walk and ended up here.
لقد خرجنا للتو للتنزه وانتهى بنا الأمر هنا.
Oh, Official Li.
أوه، لي الرسمي.
These two honored guests have powerful connections.
لهذين الضيفين الكرام علاقات قوية.
It's rare for them to visit today.
ومن النادر أن يزورونا اليوم.
There's a murder case at hand.
هناك قضية قتل في متناول اليد.
And you still want to keep the business running?
ومازلت تريد الاستمرار في العمل؟
Oh, Official Li.
أوه، لي الرسمي.
Please, have mercy on me.
من فضلك ارحمني.
I can't afford to offend any of these guests.
لا أستطيع أن أتسبب في إهانة أي من هؤلاء الضيوف.
I'm sure you're aware of that.
أنا متأكد من أنك على علم بذلك.
Madam.
سيدتي.
You've misunderstood Official Li's intentions.
لقد أسأت فهم نوايا المسؤول لي.
Official Li means, since we're already here,
لي الرسمي يعني، بما أننا هنا بالفعل،
would you really let him spend the night alone?
هل ستسمحين له حقا بقضاء الليل وحيدا؟
Of course not.
بالطبع لا.
Official Li, which courtesan do you fancy?
السيد لي الرسمي، أي العاهرة تفضل؟
I'll send her to your room right away.
سأرسلها إلى غرفتك على الفور.
Oh, Madam.
أوه سيدتي.
What he means is, his tastes are a bit unusual.
ما يعنيه هو أن أذواقه غير عادية بعض الشيء.
He doesn't like young ladies.
إنه لا يحب الفتيات الصغيرات.
He prefers older women.
يفضل النساء الأكبر سنا.
Lin Xiaoran, what nonsense are you talking?
لين شياوران، ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدثين عنه؟
So, what age does Official Li prefer?
إذن، ما هو العمر المفضل للمسؤول لي؟
The older, the better.
كلما كان عمرك أكبر، كلما كان ذلك أفضل.
Oh, you must be joking.
أوه، لا بد أنك تمزح.
Liuxiang Pavilion doesn't have women like that.
جناح ليوشيانغ لا يحتوي على نساء مثل تلك.
Then Madam herself would be perfect.
حينها ستكون السيدة نفسها مثالية.
Oh, stop making fun of me.
أوه، توقف عن السخرية مني.
Lin Xiaoran.
لين شياوران.
Yes?
نعم؟
Within ten feet.
في حدود عشرة أقدام.
Sir, isn't it obvious?
سيدي، أليس هذا واضحا؟
I heard this place used to be a deserted graveyard.
سمعت أن هذا المكان كان مقبرة مهجورة.
Wanning was clearly possessed by a ghost long ago.
من الواضح أن وانينج كان مسكونًا بشبح منذ فترة طويلة.
Wanning was one of your courtesans too.
وانينج كانت واحدة من مومساتك أيضًا.
Why are you so sure?
لماذا أنت متأكدة هكذا؟
Just look at her.
فقط أنظر إليها.
She gets prettier every day.
إنها تصبح أجمل كل يوم.
She charms the very souls out of the guests.
إنها تسحر أرواح الضيوف.
If that's not a ghost, what is it?
إذا لم يكن هذا شبحًا، فما هو؟
Sir.
سيد.
That Chunxiang just now isn't a good sort.
إن تشون شيانغ الآن ليس من النوع الجيد.
She's always jealous of Wanning.
إنها تشعر بالغيرة دائمًا من وانينج.
She wishes something would happen to Wanning's clients so she'd lose favor.
إنها تتمنى أن يحدث شيء لعملاء وانينج حتى تفقد تأييدهم.
What about you? Aren't you jealous?
ماذا عنك؟ ألا تغار؟
Me?
أنا؟
Here in Liuxiang Pavilion,
هنا في جناح Liuxiang،
I'm the least attractive of all.
أنا الأقل جاذبية من الجميع.
I'm just here to make a living.
أنا هنا فقط لكسب لقمة العيش.
Sir.
سيد.
You don't suspect I had anything to do with Wanning's death, do you?
أنت لا تشك في أن لي أي علاقة بموت وانينج، أليس كذلك؟
I'm just a weak woman.
أنا مجرد امرأة ضعيفة.
Please don't accuse an innocent person.
من فضلك لا تتهم شخصًا بريئًا.
Did Wanning act strangely at all?
هل تصرف وانينج بشكل غريب على الإطلاق؟
We all just serve our own clients.
نحن جميعا نخدم عملائنا فقط.
Who has time to care about others?
من لديه الوقت للاهتمام بالآخرين؟
Sir, my rates are quite fair.
سيدي، أسعاري عادلة جدًا.
So, how did you two living Zhuge Liangs do?
إذن، كيف كان حالكما يا تشوغي ليانغ؟
Did you find anything out?
هل وجدت شيئا؟
The deceased just now was Official Zhang from the Luoyang Protectorate.
وكان المتوفي للتو هو المسؤول تشانغ من محمية لويانغ.
He committed suicide out of guilt two years ago.
لقد انتحر بسبب شعوره بالذنب منذ عامين.
The court let his case fizzle out.
تركت المحكمة قضيته تتلاشى.
Most people who come here wear masks.
معظم الأشخاص الذين يأتون إلى هنا يرتدون أقنعة.
It's very likely
من المحتمل جدًا
they're all people who can't show their faces in daylight.
إنهم جميعًا أشخاص لا يستطيعون إظهار وجوههم في ضوء النهار.
Xun Wan's death
وفاة شون وان
is probably connected to this place too.
ربما يكون مرتبطًا بهذا المكان أيضًا.
Hey, Xiaoran.
مرحبًا، شياوران.
Yeah?
نعم؟
You've been gone for so long.
لقد كنت غائبا لفترة طويلة.
Did you find anything?
هل وجدت شيئا؟
They all claim not to know Xun Wan.
يزعمون جميعًا أنهم لا يعرفون شون وان.
I think
أظن
we need to try other methods.
نحن بحاجة إلى تجربة أساليب أخرى.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
I'm off to spend a night with someone.
سأذهب لقضاء ليلة مع شخص ما.
That brothel madam still has her charm.
لا تزال سيدة بيت الدعارة هذه تتمتع بسحرها.
I'm leaving now.
سأغادر الآن.
Official Li, aren't you coming with me?
السيد لي الرسمي، هل ستأتي معي؟
I don't like older women.
أنا لا أحب النساء الأكبر سنا.
A woman who can wield a sword and roam the world—
امرأة تستطيع استخدام السيف والتجول في العالم
Lady Shen truly makes me envious.
السيدة شين تجعلني أشعر بالحسد حقا.
How you want to live
كيف تريد أن تعيش
is your own choice.
هو اختيارك الخاص.
It has nothing to do with being male or female.
ليس له علاقة بكونك ذكرًا أو أنثى.
Miss Shen put it well.
لقد قالت السيدة شين ذلك بشكل جيد.
I hope that one day
أتمنى أن يحدث هذا يوما ما
we can roam the world like Miss Shen.
يمكننا أن نجوب العالم مثل الآنسة شين.
Wanning is dead.
وانينج مات.
You two seem to get along better now.
يبدو أنكما تتفقان بشكل أفضل الآن.
She deserved to die anyway.
لقد استحقت الموت على أية حال.
If not for her,
إن لم تكن لها،
we wouldn't be scolded for not being as pretty.
لن نتعرض للتوبيخ لعدم كوننا جميلات.
Madam wouldn't beat and scold us every day.
لن تضربنا السيدة وتوبخنا كل يوم.
Sorry to keep everyone waiting.
آسف لإبقاء الجميع في انتظار.
The Liuxiang Pavilion contest will now continue.
ستستمر الآن مسابقة جناح ليوشيانغ.
Great, wonderful!
رائع، رائع!
Good, good.
حسنًا، حسنًا.
Good.
جيد.
This...
هذا...
What is this?
ما هذا؟
Oh no, this won't do.
أوه لا، هذا لن ينجح.
Would you choose this one?
هل ستختار هذا؟
No interest, it's embarrassing.
لا يوجد اهتمام، إنه أمر محرج.
Not interested, right?
غير مهتم، أليس كذلك؟
Such a letdown.
مثل هذا خيبة الأمل.
Couldn't you find someone prettier?
هل لم تجدي شخصا أجمل؟
Is this even presentable? Are there no ladies left?
هل هذا لائقٌ حقًا؟ ألم يبقَ هناك نساء؟
I don't want it, you take it.
لا أريده، خذه أنت.
I don't want it either.
أنا لا أريد ذلك أيضًا.
Whoever wants it can keep it.
من يريده يستطيع الاحتفاظ به.
No, no.
لا لا.
Change it, please.
غيّره من فضلك.
Hey, Official Li.
مرحبًا، يا مسؤول لي.
Official Li.
لي الرسمي.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Listen, this lady likes me.
اسمع، هذه السيدة تحبني.
I don't have enough money, lend me some.
ليس لدي ما يكفي من المال، أقرضني بعضًا منه.
This...
هذا...
This isn't enough money.
هذا ليس ما يكفي من المال.
What do you take our Madam for?
لماذا تأخذ سيدتنا؟
Be generous, be generous!
كن كريما، كن كريما!
Don't go overboard.
لا تبالغ.
Be generous.
كن كريما.
Is this enough?
هل هذا كافي؟
Isn't this too much?
أليس هذا كثيرًا جدًا؟
It's just right.
إنه على حق تماما.
So expensive!
غالية الثمن!
Honored guest, please.
ضيف الشرف من فضلك.
Wait for my news.
انتظر اخباري
Remember,
يتذكر،
you must leave before the candle burns out.
يجب عليك المغادرة قبل أن تحترق الشمعة.
Your money only covers this one candle.
أموالك تغطي هذه الشمعة فقط.
Sir, you're really handsome.
سيدي، أنت وسيم حقا.
Will you help me undress?
هل ستساعدني في خلع ملابسي؟
Sure.
بالتأكيد.
Aren't you afraid there's a female ghost under my mask?
ألا تخاف من وجود شبح أنثى تحت قناعي؟
Why not enjoy a night with a ghost?
لماذا لا تستمتع بليلة مع شبح؟
Sir, don't let the candle go out.
سيدي، لا تدع الشمعة تنطفئ.
Rules are meant to be broken.
القواعد موجودة ليتم كسرها.
Quick, undress, undress!
سريعًا، اخلع ملابسك، اخلع ملابسك!
You're so naughty.
أنت شقي جدًا.
You're annoying.
أنت مزعج.
Alright, alright.
حسناً حسناً.
I'm done playing, untie me.
لقد انتهيت من اللعب، أطلق سراحي.
Oh, sir!
يا سيدي!
Now that you're here, I don't plan to let you go.
الآن بعد أن أصبحت هنا، لا أخطط للسماح لك بالرحيل.
Miss, I'm really not here for fun today.
آنسة، أنا لست هنا من أجل المتعة اليوم.
I have something to ask you.
عندي شيء أريد أن أسألك عنه.
Oh, it's fine.
أوه، إنه بخير.
We can talk while we play, it's no problem.
يمكننا التحدث أثناء اللعب، فلا مشكلة.
I'm sorry, isn't that enough?
أنا آسف، أليس هذا كافيا؟
How about this: there's a handsome, rich man outside.
ماذا عن هذا: هناك رجل وسيم وغني بالخارج.
I'll introduce him to you.
سأقدمه لك.
Alright, what do you want to ask?
حسنًا، ماذا تريد أن تسأل؟
Untie me first.
أطلقني أولاً.
Has this man, Xun Wan, ever been here?
هل كان هذا الرجل، شون وان، هنا من قبل؟
Oh, I think I've seen him.
أوه، أعتقد أنني رأيته.
But that's not his name.
ولكن هذا ليس اسمه.
Huh?
هاه؟
Official Li, someone else has died.
المسؤول لي، شخص آخر قد مات.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
When did it happen?
متى حدث ذلك؟
Just now.
الآن.
We just saw Wanning.
لقد رأينا وانينج للتو.
She killed Chunxiang and Qiulan.
لقد قتلت Chunxiang و Qiulan.
Are you sure it was Wanning?
هل أنت متأكد من أنه وانينج؟
Chunxiang, Qiulan.
تشونشيانغ، تشيولان.
They just told me,
لقد قالوا لي فقط،
that after Wanning died, they'd finally have their chance.
أنه بعد وفاة وانينج، سيكون لديهم أخيرًا فرصتهم.
Don't spread the word about this yet.
لا تنشر الكلمة عن هذا بعد.
Who is it?
من هذا؟
It's me. Do you think I'm a ghost?
أنا. هل تعتقد أنني شبح؟
Were you really possessed?
هل كنت ممسوسا حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
What did she talk to you about?
ماذا تحدثت معك عنه؟
Romance and lovers' bonds.
الرومانسية وروابط العشاق.
Do you want to hear?
هل تريد أن تسمع؟
Official.
رسمي.
Official, help us!
يا رسمي ساعدونا!
Two more courtesans have died.
لقد توفيت اثنتان أخريان من العاهرات.
What should we do?
ماذا يجب علينا أن نفعل؟
Please save us, Official.
من فضلك أنقذنا يا رسمي.
The female ghost here—
الشبح الأنثى هنا—
She won't let us go.
انها لن تسمح لنا بالذهاب.
There are no ghosts in this world.
لا يوجد أشباح في هذا العالم.
And ghosts don't kill people.
والأشباح لا تقتل الناس.
But the courtesans all saw it.
لكن جميع العاهرات رأين ذلك.
Did someone named Xun Wan come here?
هل جاء شخص اسمه شون وان إلى هنا؟
I'm not sure about that.
أنا لست متأكدة من ذلك.
Guests here all use fake names.
جميع الضيوف هنا يستخدمون أسماء وهمية.
Announce to the guests—
أعلن للضيوف—
the contest will proceed as usual.
ستستمر المسابقة كالمعتاد.
But—
لكن-
We're all waiting for the ghost to show up again.
نحن جميعا ننتظر ظهور الشبح مرة أخرى.
Relax.
يستريح.
Since those officials gave the order,
وبما أن هؤلاء المسؤولين أصدروا الأمر،
the bidding can't be stopped.
لا يمكن إيقاف المزايدة.
I'm counting on you now.
أنا أعتمد عليك الآن.
Now that Wanning is dead,
الآن بعد أن مات وانينج،
those high-ranking officials
هؤلاء المسؤولين رفيعي المستوى
will surely pay you endless silver.
سوف تدفع لك بالتأكيد فضة لا نهاية لها.
You should thank me properly.
ينبغي عليك أن تشكرني بشكل صحيح.
Enough.
كافٍ.
Ghost! Ghost!
شبح! شبح!
Official Li! Ghost! Ghost!
لي الرسمي! شبح! شبح!
Yunjin, you wretched slave!
يونجين، أيها العبد البائس!
Coming.
آت.
Will you take it off yourself, or should I do it?
هل ستزيله بنفسك أم ينبغي لي أن أفعل ذلك؟
Wanning.
وانينغ.
Why is it you?
لماذا انت؟